Hello friends, welcome to 51 once again.
I have selected
IC IC Eye Long on the weekly time frame here.
Now see, today ICEC
Long is trying to stay on a good time frame.
Now, let me try to
show you a little bit here. Look at its
level. As it did,
it had
also cut a candle pattern in a way. Or see,
it had a good resistance zone
which it crossed from here and
as soon as it broke out from here,
look, now it had formed an M pattern here.
But look, right now it is
visible on your weekly time frame. As
I put the day time frame here,
look, a different scene happens here. Look, as
I put it on the day time frame, then
see, it is first class. It is
trying to form a double pattern. In a
way, again, look, and it is
trying to cut. So from here, today a  It has
also seen a good amount of movement. You see, it
closed at 1388 and somewhere it was already
facing resistance at this zone for quite some time,
but it is possible from here that the journey ahead can
continue, so you guys
keep an eye on it, friends, let me
try to put a little bit of TCS in front of you guys,
friends, in TCS, I will
try to show it here in the weekly time frame,
see,
it has already been facing TCS like a resistance for many weeks, see,
now you will see one time, two times, three times, four times
and this five
times almost, it is giving respect to its tents in a
way, but now
if you remove TCS from the weekly time frame and
put it in the day time frame, then
you will see in the day time frame, it had
tried to cut by making an M pattern,
but today if you
look at its time, some scenario is visible, that is what
I am showing.  Just tell
you, today they have given a strong
movement of around 1 to 1.5,
friends, if the meaning of M baton cutting is
that if it had to go down, then it would have
tried to come down like this,
but here today they have
given a positive movement which
somewhere indicates that it can move upwards from here
because in the meantime there was a
lot of news as you know that there was a buy back
going on in the markets, so
keep a little eye on this as well, it is possible that
in the coming time it can give a good movement from here,
friends, I have just
taken Bajaj Fishers here, you see what
scenario is visible of it on the weekly time frame,
see Bajaj Fishers is one of
them, since its split,
see from here it is trying to make a different type of
bench,
see here, somewhere a triangle
pattern is being seen which is acting almost
like this, somewhere it is gradually increasing its size,
see, it is gradually decreasing
and from here it can happen  It
can break out somewhere upwards or downwards. The maximum
chance is that friends, he is
trying to reduce his size. It can be that there is a
greater
chance that it will go up somewhere. So
you can also keep an eye on Bajaj Fisher.
It can also give a good return in the coming time.
Friends, now the one I have selected here
is PTC India. Now see, it is trying to
hold at a very important place.
Friends, see this,
on the weekly time frame, it is already getting so much
resistance. Now
see, one time or two times it had remained a
little behind but this
three time, four time and this five time it has come again and
tried to
touch the resistance. As you friends, you all
know that whenever the price is touching or hitting any resistance or
support repeatedly,
it
means that somewhere the resistance is weakening.
If it is hitting support repeatedly, then the
support is weakening. So, the
situation here right now is that this
maximum time that they have seen, it is
trying to hit the resistance,
so there is a high chance that PTC
India may have a good strong movement upwards from here.
I will just put a little date time
frame here,
look at it in the day time frame, a good round
up pattern type is visible on the day time frame, I am showing this to
you, see,
as if a day time frame is trying to form a round up pattern
type, so it can happen
as you can see from here, it
came here like this, so it is possible that in the
coming few days it can consolidate a little here and
give an upward movement, so
you
people have made a little bit above it here, it is also
possible that from here a
good profit can be given in the short time.
Friends, if you like my video,
please like, share and subscribe.
Friends, see you tomorrow with a new video.
Thank you friends ba bye